Guide to the American Guild of Musical Artists Records WAG.209
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
American Guild of Musical Artists Records
1918-2007
1935-1965
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
American Guild of Musical Artists
Mays, Linda
WAG.209
15 Linear Feet (16 boxes)
3 websites in 3 archived websites.
The American Guild of Musical Artists (AGMA) was founded in 1936 in New York City to protect the interests of solo musical artists in the field of opera and later expanded to include dancers, choreographers and some categories of stage managers. The union became affiliated with the Associated Actors and Artistes of America (known as the 4A's) and established regional offices throughout the United States in addition to the main New York office. The records of two predecessor organizations, the Grand Opera Artists Association and the Grand Opera Choral Alliance comprise the earliest material in the collection. The bulk of the collection consists of the papers of AGMA's New York office, including correspondence, bargaining files and agreements, arbitration files, internal structure, member correspondence, an early membership ledger, clippings, convention Proceedings, scrapbooks, and records of guest status fees paid by artists from abroad. There are also a number of files documenting AGMA's relations with other theatrical unions, and many failed attempts at mergers between members of the 4A's.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by the American Guild of Musical Artists, via an agreement with president Linda Mays, in 2002. The accession number associated with this gift is 2002.008.
https://www.musicalartists.org/ was initially selected by curators and captured through the use of The California Digital Library's Web Archiving Service in 2007 as part of the Labor Unions and Organizations (U.S.). In 2015, this website was migrated to Archive-It. Archive-It uses web crawling technology to capture websites at a scheduled time and displays only an archived copy, from the resulting WARC file, of the website. In 2019, http://www.agmafunds.org/ was added. The accession number associated with this website is 2019.138. In 2020, https://agmarelief.org/ was added. The accession number associated with this website is 2020.034.
Historical/Biographical Note
The American Guild of Musical Artists (AGMA) was founded March 11, 1936 by a prominent group of solo musical artists including Lawrence Tibbett, Alma Gluck and Jascha Heifetz. Tibbett was to serve as AGMA's president and Heifetz and Gluck as vice-presidents. Among the founding members were Kirsten Flagstad, John McCormack, Andres Segovia, George Gershwin, Fred Waring and Paul Whiteman. The advisory board included Walter Damrosch, Lauritz Melchoir, Ezio Pinza, and Lily Pons, among others. By joining together, these pioneers hoped to eliminate unfair practices and abuses that were all too prevalent in their profession. Often artists would perform without being paid, or would play out of town and be stranded without transportation back home; rehearsal time was unpaid and there was no limitation on the number of performances an artist could be called upon to give each week. AGMA negotiations came to include pay, terms of employment and workplace conditions, as well as the efforts by the union to promote common aims and interests of the artists, and to foster the musical arts and musical culture in general.
In August 1937, AGMA became an affiliate of the Associated Actors and Artistes of America (known as the 4A's), a federation of AFL-CIO theatrical unions. At that time, the organization merged with an older union, the Grand Opera Artists Association, which previously had held the 4A's charter. In the spring of 1938, AGMA also incorporated the Grand Opera Choral Alliance, an organization that represented opera choristers and had already established a bargaining relationship with the Metropolitan Opera. Thus strengthened, AGMA signed its first collective bargaining agreement with the Metropolitan Opera in August 1938 and became the Met artists' sole bargaining agent.
During the 1940s, AGMA expanded its jurisdiction, negotiating contracts with numerous opera companies throughout the United States. Sick leave and social security benefits were among the goals of the organization, and the union established its own Relief Fund to assist aged and disabled members; the Fund was financed by the Theatre Authority, for many years a clearing house for theatrica benefit performances and other fund-raising. With solid gains having been made in larger opera companies, AGMA turned in the 1950s to the growing field of regional opera as well as to popular professional touring choral groups.
During the 1960s, AGMA was highly visible in lobbying efforts for federal support for the arts, an important feature of both the Kennedy and Johnson administrations. To accommodate performers at the New York World's Fair a "guest status" category was developed and later offered to foreign touring companies like the Moiseyev Dance Company. In 1964 a landmark agreement was negotiated with the Metropolitan Opera guaranteeing 52 weeks for the entire shop. Union contracts were also designed for summer apprentice programs with companies like the Lake George Summer Festival, the Santa Fe Opera, the Chautauqua Institute, and the Central City Festival.
With ballet emerging as a popular entertainment form during the early 1960s, dancers in smaller touring and regional dance companies sought union protection. By the late 1960s the importance of dance to AGMA's jurisdiction was growing, as new dance companies (some representing innovative, non-traditional forms of dance) were being organized in many locales across the country. By the 1980s, ballet dancers comprised about 50 per cent of AGMA's membership and the ballet and dance fields have continued to expand steadily. In 1986 AGMA had 5,500 members, 3,000 of whom were based in New York City. There were ten area offices located throughout the United States, negotiating contracts and handling local problems within their regions. Although AGMA's jurisdiction did not extend to Canada, the association has maintained an office in Toronto to serve as a liaison with Canadian Equity.
Performing arts administration in both opera and dance has becoming increasingly corporate in its outlook and goals in recent years, with less professional theater experience represented in management. By 1990 there were fewer than ten opera companies in the United States that presented more than twelve productions a year; the rest staged from one to six productions.
Membership in AGMA is open to all interested parties, regardless of prior experience, affiliation or nationality. Many performers hold joint membership in other 4As-affiliated unions such as AFTRA, SAG, and Actors' Equity.
Scope and Content Note
Series I: Convention Proceedings, 1948-1962. This series is available on microfilm (R-7427, reels 46-49). Researchers must use microfilm.
Series II: General Files, 1918-1993, comprises the bulk of the collection. The vast majority of General Files contain material from the New York AGMA office, including bargaining files, arbitrations, member correspondence, and communications with regional offices, with managers, with venues and companies, and with other unions. They also contain background or research material on related organizations, events, and notable individuals. There is a small amount of Board of Governors meeting minutes, 1938-1944 (partially duplicating minutes available on microfilm; see note under Series I), as well as agendas for board meetings, 1947-1955. General correspondence is filed by year and includes incoming and outgoing letters; these files document the administrations of AGMA presidents Lawrence Tibbett, John Brownlee, George London, Cornell MacNeil and Gene Boucher, with a few files dating from a later period. The records of two predecessor organizations, the Grand Opera Choral Alliance and the Grand Opera Artists Association of America, are located alphabetically within the General Files and represent some of the earliest material in the collection.
Series III: Guest Status Fees, c.1965-1991 (mostly 1970s), contains standard paperwork required of foreign dance companies wishing to perform in AGMA's jurisdiction.
Series IV: Oversize Scrapbooks and Ledger, 1936-1951, consists of a scrapbook of publicity clippings, 1936 and 1950-1951; a ledger of cash receipts (dues), 1938-1940; and a scrapbook containing dues cards, c.1936-1940, filed alphabetically.
Series V: Archived Websites, consists the websites for the the AGMA retirement and health funds and the main AGMA website, dating back since 2007.
Arrangement
Series I and IV are arranged chronologically; series II and III are arranged alphabetically.
Organized into five series:
I, Convention Proceedings (These files have been microfilmed.)
II, General Files
III, Guest Status Fees
IV, Oversize Scrapbooks and Ledger
V, Archived Websites
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Records of the American Guild of Variety Artists (WAG 095)
Records of Actors' Equity Association (WAG 011)
Records of Associated Actors and Artistes of America (WAG 110)
Separated Material
A few photographs and graphic items were separated to the Non-Print Department of the Tamiment Library.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Due to the fragile nature of the original materials, researchers must use the microfilmed version of Series I: Convention Records; microfilm call number is R-7427, reels 46-49.
In addition, a small amount of Board of Governors meeting minutes, 1938-1944, in Series II: General Files are also available on microfilm. Microfilm call number is R-7427, reels 1-46.
Take Down Policy
Archived websites are made accessible for purposes of education and research. NYU Libraries have given attribution to rights holders when possible; however, due to the nature of archival collections, we are not always able to identify this information.
If you hold the rights to materials in our archived websites that are unattributed, please let us know so that we may maintain accurate information about these materials.
If you are a rights holder and are concerned that you have found material on this website for which you have not granted permission (or is not covered by a copyright exception under US copyright laws), you may request the removal of the material from our site by submitting a notice, with the elements described below, to the special.collections@nyu.edu.
Please include the following in your notice: Identification of the material that you believe to be infringing and information sufficient to permit us to locate the material; your contact information, such as an address, telephone number, and email address; a statement that you are the owner, or authorized to act on behalf of the owner, of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed and that you have a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; a statement that the information in the notification is accurate and made under penalty of perjury; and your physical or electronic signature. Upon receiving a notice that includes the details listed above, we will remove the allegedly infringing material from public view while we assess the issues identified in your notice.
Musicians -- Labor unions -- United States.; Performing arts -- United States.; Ballet -- New York (State) -- New York; Collective labor agreements |x Singers |z United States.; Labor unions |z New York (State) |z New York |x Jurisdictional disputes.; Opera |z United States |x History.; Reports.; Clippings (information artifacts); Opera -- New York (State) New York; Choral singing |z New York (State) |z New York.; Correspondence.; Agreements.; New York (N.Y.).; Minutes (administrative records); Legal documents.; Associated Actors and Artistes of America; American Federation of Musicians; Gluck, Alma, 1884-1938; Actors' Equity Association; Grand Opera Choral Alliance; Grand Opera Artists Association; American Guild of Variety Artists; American Federation of Television and Radio Artists; Metropolitan Opera (New York, N.Y.); Heifetz, Jascha, 1901-1987; Boucher, Gene; Tibbett, Lawrence, 1896-1960; American Guild of Musical Artists; Mays, Linda
- Series I: Convention Records, 1948-1962
  - Convention Proceedings (a.m.), Jan 8, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Convention Proceedings (p.m.), Jan 8, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Convention Proceedings (p.m.), Jan 8, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Convention Proceedings (a.m.), Jan 9, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Convention Proceedings (p.m.), Jan 9, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Convention Proceedings (p.m.), Jan 9, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Convention Proceedings (a.m.), Jan 10, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Convention Proceedings (p.m.), Jan 10, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Convention Proceedings, Jan 10, 1948-Jan 11, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Convention Proceedings (a.m.), Jan 20, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Convention Proceedings (p.m.), Jan 20, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Convention Proceedings (p.m.), Jan 20, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Convention Proceedings (a.m.), Jan 21, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Convention Proceedings (p.m.), Jan 21, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Convention Proceedings (p.m.), Jan 21, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Convention Proceedings (a.m.), Jan 22, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Convention Proceedings (p.m.), Jan 22, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Convention Proceedings (a.m.), Jun 16, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Convention Proceedings (p.m.), Jun 16, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Convention Proceedings (p.m.), Jun 16, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Convention Proceedings (a.m.), Jun 17, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Convention Proceedings (p.m.), Jun 17, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Convention Proceedings (p.m.), Jun 17, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Convention Proceedings (a.m.), Jun 18, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Convention Proceedings (p.m.), Jun 18, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Convention Proceedings, Dec 1, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Convention Proceedings (a.m.), Dec 2, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Convention Proceedings (p.m.), Dec 2, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Convention Proceedings: Exhibits, Dec 1, 1962-Dec 2, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Convention Proceedings: Minutes, Dec 1, 1962-Dec 2, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Series II: General Files, 1918-1993
  - Actors' Equity Association, 1937-1937 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Actors' Equity Association, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Actors' Equity Association//AGMA Agreement: Committee data, correspondence, 1939-1952 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Actors' Equity Association: Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Actors' Equity Association: Jurisdiction, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Actors' Equity Association: Re: AGMA organizing in the Bay Area, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Affiliation with foreign unions, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Agency fees, 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Agreement re: Foreign attractions, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Airlines anti-trust litigation, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Air quality solutions: Green Circle Solutions, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Agmagazine, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Agreements, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Agreements, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Agreements, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Agreements, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Agreements: AEA, Canadian AEA, AGMA, and FAAC, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Agreements: Impresario contract, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Agreements: Managers' contract, 1944-1949 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Agreements: Metropolitan Opera, 1940-1950 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Agreements: Metropolitan Opera, 1952-1958 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Agreements: Metropolitan Opera, 1961-1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Agreements: Metropolitan Opera, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Agreements: Metropolitan Opera Association, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Agreements: Metropolitan Opera: Trust agreement, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Agreements: Robin Hood Dell Concerts, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Agreements: National Educational Television and Radio Center and AFTRA, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - American Ballet Theatre, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - American Ballet Theatre: Overseas riders, 1954-1980 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - American Federation of Actors, 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - American Federation of Labor, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - American Federation of Labor: Convention Proceedings, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - American Federation of Labor: Four A's International Board, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - American Federation of Musicians, 1942-1944, 1949-1953 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - American Federation of Musicians/AGMA: Agreement, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - American Federation of Musicians: AGMA, et al. v. James Petrillo and AFM, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - American Federation of Musicians: James Petrillo, 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - American Federation of Musicians: James Petrillo: Clippings, 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - American Federation of Radio Artists, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - AGMA-AFTRA merger, 1981-1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - AGMA-AFTRA merger, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - AGMA-AFTRA merger: Drafts of memoranda, etc., 1982 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - AGMA-AFTRA merger: Dues and finances, 1977-1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - AGMA-AFTRA merger: Gene Boucher, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - AGMA-AFTRA merger: Negotiations and correspondence, 1977-1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - AGMA-AFTRA merger: Proposals and draft agreements, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - AGMA-Equity agreement re: Equity League Pension Trust, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - AGMA-Equity radio program: List of potential sponsors, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - AGMA Handbook changes: Work copies and proofs, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - AGMA Merit Awards (Listings, etc.), 1960-1978 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - AGMA Pension and Welfare Funds: Agreement and Declaration of Trust, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - American Guild of Variety Artists (AGVA), 1939, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - American Lyric Theatre, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - American Society of Composers, Artists, and Publishers (ASCAP), 1982 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - ASCAP, 1961-1966 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - ASCAP, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - ASCAP, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - American Theatre Wing, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Annual Meeting, 1943-1975 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Anti-trust suit against CAMI, NCA, et al.: Consent decree, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Application forms, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Arbitration, 1954, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration: AGVA v. American Pop'ra Company and Adele Holzer, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Arbitration: AGMA v. Artists International (Claims re: Harrison, Ruffino, Englebright), 1976-1983 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Arbitration: AGMA v. Connecticut Opera (Grado and Campora), 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration: AGMA v. Metropolitan Opera Association (Knie), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration: AGMA v. New York City Opera, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration: AGMA v. Palm Beach Opera (Campora and Grado), 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Arbitration: AGMA v. Palm Beach Opera (Farley and Kusiak), 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Arbitration: AGMA v. Providence Opera Theatre, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Arbitration: AGMA v. Providence Opera Theatre (DiGiuseppe and Lambrinos), 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Arbitration: AGMA v. Providence Opera Theatre (dues deductions), 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Arbitration: AGMA v. Providence Opera Theatre (Dworchak and Bilbao), 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Arbitration: AGMA v. Providence Opera Theatre (Powell), 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Arbitration: AGMA v. Tulsa Opera (Maralin Niska), 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Arbitration: Metropolitan Opera (Shinall), 1979-1983 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Arbitration: NYC Opera: "Force Majeure" case, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Arbitration: Plowright, R. v. Los Angeles Music Center Opera, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Arbitration: Robertson, Toby, 1983-1986 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Arbitration: San Francisco Opera, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Arbitration: Schell, W., 1981-1986 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Assad, James: Grievance against Opera Company of Philadelphia, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Assessment Committee, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America, 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America, 1959, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America: Correspondence, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America: Jurisdiction Committee, 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America: Merger proposals, 1948-1952 (Box 5, Folder 1A)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America: Minutes, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America: Minutes, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America: Report on Consolidation, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America: Television Committee, 1949-1952 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America vs. IATSE, Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Association of Theatrical Agents and Managers, 1942-1943 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Audition notices, 1977, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Auditions: Chicago, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo: Denham matter, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Ballet: Special Committee on, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 10A)
  - Ballet Theatre, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Ballet Theatre: Delegates, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Becker and London: Dues letters, 1981-1992 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Becker, London, Russow: Legal, 1991-1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Bernard Reis and Company, 1943-1944 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Board Entitlement, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Board Entitlement Study: AGMA election count, 1967-1978 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Board of Governors, 1940-1941 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Board of Governors, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Board of Governors, 1944, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Board of Governors, 1969-1983 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Board of Governors: Hearings, 1959-1982 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Board Resolution: Maria Callas, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Board Resolutions: Charges against members, 1960-1962 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Board Resolutions: Charges against Frederick Foster, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Board resumes, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Board resumes, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Board resumes, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Board resumes, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Board resumes, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Board resumes, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Board resumes: Faine, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Board resumes: Faine, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Boosey and Hawkes, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Boucher, Gene, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Brands Mart, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn Opera Company, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Bulletins, 1936-1938 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Bulletins, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Bulletins, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Campaign Literature, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Canadian Actors' Equity Association, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Casei, Nedda, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Certificate of Incorporation, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Charters, 1937-1939 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Chicago Opera Company, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Choral Auditions, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Choral Committee: Minutes, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 15)